Welcome to an introduction to Data Science with Python.
歡迎來到介紹Python中的數據科學課程。
This course is the first course out of five in a larger Python and
本課程是五門課程中的第一門課程，在更寬廣的Python
Data Science Specialization.
和數據科學專業化課程。
Each course progressively builds on your knowledge from previous courses to give
每門課程逐漸建立在以往課程的知識基礎之上，
you a well-rounded view of what Data Science is, while helping you to
讓您全面了解數據科學是什麼，同時幫助您
develop skills to practice data science.
發展實踐數據科學的技能。
The specialization is of an intermediate level or difficulty, and
這專業化課程是中級水平的難度，
we expect that you have studied some basic programming and statistics in the past.
我們期望你過去研究了一些基本的程式設計和統計。
In this specialization,
在這個專業化課程中，
we're focused on teaching applied skills using the Python programming language.
我們專注於教授應用技能使用Python程式語言。
There are many other tools that one can use in data science,
還有許多其他可以在數據科學中使用的工具，
such as specialized statistical analysis languages like R, or
比如專門的統計分析語言像R，
more general purpose programming languages like Java and C.
或者更通用的程式語言像Java和C。
We chose Python as the basis for this specialization for three reasons.
我們選擇Python作為這個專業化課程的基礎有三個原因。
First, it's easy to learn.
首先，很容易學習。
Python is now the language of choice for
Python現在是首選的語言在
introducing university students to programming.
介紹大學生程式語言。
It's used in eight out of 10 of the US's top computer science programs.
它被用於美國頂尖計算機科學課程中的十個的八個。
Python programs tend to have minimal templating that you've might have seen in
Python程式傾向於具有您可能看到的最少模板的，
other languages, and
相比於其他語言，
have more natural constructs for typical tasks you might need to accomplish.
並且具有更多的自然結構，用來完成您可能需要的典型任務。
If you have programming experience, but
如果你有軟體經驗，而
not Python-specific experience, you can pick up Python very quickly.
不是特定Python的經驗，你可以很快地學習到Python。
Second, it's full featured.
二，它的功能齊全。
Python is a very general programming language with a lot of built-in
Python是一種非常通用的程式語言，具有大量內置
libraries and excels at manipulating data, network programming, and databases.
的程式庫，高超的數據操縱，網路程式和資料庫。
It's mature,
它是很成熟的，
and there's plenty of resources available from books to online courses.
有很多資源可用，從書籍到在線課程。
Finally, Python has a significant set of data science libraries one can use.
最後，Python有一組很重要的數據科學程式庫。
The base of these is called the SciPy Ecosystem, and
它們的基礎叫做SciPy生態系統(Ecosystem)，
it even has its own conference series.
甚至有自己的聚會系列。
Both the interface that we're going to use for doing assignments,
兩者，我們將用於做作業的介面，
called Jupiter Notebooks, and the main libraries for
稱為Jupiter Notebook，以及，主要的程式庫
the first two courses, Pandas and Matplotlib, are part of the SciPy stack,
在前兩個課程，Pandas和Matplotlib，都是SciPy程式的一部分，
and provide an excellent basis for moving into machine learning, text mining and
它提供了良好的基礎為進入機器學習，文件挖掘和
network analysis.
網路分析。
This first course is broken into four modules.
這第一次課程分為四個模組。
The first module focuses on getting prerequisites in place and
第一個模組重點是獲得必要先決條件，
reviews some of the basics of the Python language.
並回顧Python語言的一些基本知識。
Don't worry, if you already have Python down and you want to be challenged,
不要擔心，如果你已經學習了Python，而且你想要受到挑戰，
we have some advanced Python in here as well.
我們在這裡也有一些先進的Python。
The advanced Python isn't strictly necessary for
高級Python並不是絕對必要的，在
the rest of the specialization, but many of these examples you might see on the web
其餘的專業化課程裡。但是對於您可能在網路上看到的許多範例
or broader data science topics like Big Data and real-time analytics,
或更廣泛的數據科學主題，如大數據(BigData)和即時(RealTime)分析，
might require a knowledge of some of these more specialized features.
可能需要了解其中這一些更特別的功能。
In the second module we're going to dig into the pandas Toolkit.
在第二個模組中，我們將深入Pandas工具包。
The pandas Toolkit is a fundamental in Python data science, and
Pandas工具包是Python數據科學的基礎，
provides a data structure for thinking about data in a tabular form.
並提供了一種資料結構，以表格形式思考資料
This Toolkit helps bring functionality that exists in R into the Python world.
該工具包有助於將R程式中存在的功能，帶入Python世界。
It's seen significant adoption over the last five years.
在過去五年中，它被廣泛應用。
Much of the thinking behind pandas is similar to relational theory.
Pandas背後的大部分思想與關連式理論相似。
So if you have a background in databases,
所以如果你有一個資料庫的背景，
you'll find the pandas environment fairly natural to work in.
你會發現Pandas是很自然的工作環境。
At the same time, some of the more advanced ways to query and
同時，一些更先進的方式來查詢和
manipulate pandas' data frames like boolean masking and hierarchical indexing
操縱Pandas的DataFrame，如布林遮蔽(boolean masking)和層次索引(index)
are different than in databases and require some careful discussion.
不同於在資料庫中，需要一些仔細的討論。
So we'll discuss these in module three of this course.
所以我們將在本課程的第三課中討論這些。
The final module of the course is dedicated to the course project
課程的最後一個專門用於課程專案項目，
where you'll take some datasets, merge and
您將獲取一些資料集，合併和
clean them, then process the data and answer some questions.
清理它們，然後處理資料並回答一些問題。
In this week we'll discuss basic statistical tests and
在這個星期，我們將討論基本的統計測試和
methods that ensure you have a solid grasp going forward into the next course.
方法，確保您有紮實的理解前進到在下一個課程。
At the same time the intent is for
同時，目的是在
your course project to be a demonstration of the skills that you've gained
您的課程專案項目裡，表現你已經獲得了需要的技能，
in manipulating messy data into something of coherence.
在處理混亂的資料，使變成一致相干的數據。
Before we go into programming fundamentals, though, we'll talk a bit
在我們進入程式設計基礎之前，我們將更
more about what data science is, and why it's sweeping over the world.
多地談談什麼是數據科學，以及為什麼它遍布世界。